{
    "subject": "Charles_XV_of_Sweden",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Louise_of_the_Netherlands",
    "human_readable": "Charles XV of Sweden is married to Louise of the Netherlands.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9612586498260498,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Charles XV of Sweden and Louise of the Netherlands?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9523634910583496,
            "question": "To whom was Charles XV of Sweden married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.950872540473938,
            "question": "Who was married to Charles XV of Sweden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.950107991695404,
            "question": "Was Charles XV of Sweden married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8929137587547302,
            "question": "Who was Louise of the Netherlands married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8404057025909424,
            "question": "What is the name of Charles XV of Sweden's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6111115217208862,
            "question": "Where was Charles XV of Sweden king?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6005189418792725,
            "question": "Is Charles XV of Sweden from a royal family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5747519731521606,
            "question": "What country was Louise of the Netherlands from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5687724947929382,
            "question": "Is Louise of the Netherlands related to the Dutch Royal Family?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charles XV of Sweden is married to Louise of the Netherlands.",
            "html": "yago_27820_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country was Louise of the Netherlands from?",
            "html": "yago_27820_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Charles XV of Sweden from a royal family?",
            "html": "yago_27820_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Charles XV of Sweden king?",
            "html": "yago_27820_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27820_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27820_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27820_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27820_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27820_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27820_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27820_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27820_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27820_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27820_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents contain information about the marriage between Charles XV of Sweden and Louise of the Netherlands, stating that they had two children together (Louise Josephine Eugenie and Carl Oscar William Frederick) and were married for 20 years before Louise's death. The context also provides details about their family relationships and historical events surrounding their marriage, which supports the triple statement \"Charles XV of Sweden is married to Louise of the Netherlands\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Charles XV of Sweden and his marriage to Louise of the Netherlands, including details such as their children and dates. This supports the statement that Charles XV of Sweden was married to Louise of the Netherlands."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}